{
    "subject": "resource/Salah_Mansour",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/isPrimaryTopicOf",
    "object": "http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Salah_Mansour",
    "human_readable": "Salah Mansour is the primary topic of Wikipedia page 'Salah Mansour'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9874227046966553,
            "question": "Who is the primary topic of the Wikipedia page 'Salah Mansour'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9698808193206787,
            "question": "Is there a Wikipedia page dedicated to Salah Mansour?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9518992304801941,
            "question": "What is the title of the Wikipedia page about Salah Mansour?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9516061544418335,
            "question": "What is the name of the Wikipedia page about Salah Mansour?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9238596558570862,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Salah Mansour based on his Wikipedia page?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9137415289878845,
            "question": "What kind of person is Salah Mansour based on his Wikipedia page?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9131485223770142,
            "question": "What information can be found on Salah Mansour's Wikipedia page?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.800484836101532,
            "question": "Is Salah Mansour a notable figure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6993546485900879,
            "question": "Are there any notable achievements or events associated with Salah Mansour?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5829514265060425,
            "question": "How can I learn more about Salah Mansour?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Salah Mansour is the primary topic of Wikipedia page 'Salah Mansour'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_220_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable achievements or events associated with Salah Mansour?",
            "html": "dbpedia_220_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Salah Mansour a notable figure?",
            "html": "dbpedia_220_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What information can be found on Salah Mansour's Wikipedia page?",
            "html": "dbpedia_220_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_220_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_220_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_220_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_220_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_220_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_220_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_220_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_220_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_220_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_220_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The query asks whether Salah Mansour is the primary topic of a Wikipedia page \"Salah Mansour\".\n\nHere's the evaluation:\n\n* The context documents contain multiple sections and subheadings, including \"Egyptian artist\", \"Salah Mansour\", and \"Personal Life\" that all refer to Salah Mansour as the primary subject.\n* There are no contradictory statements or information about other individuals being the primary topic of a Wikipedia page with the title \"Salah Mansour\".\n\nTherefore, based on the provided context documents:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents contain extensive information about Salah Mansour, including his career as an artist, contributions to Egyptian art, personal life, and early works. This information strongly supports the statement that Salah Mansour is the primary topic of a Wikipedia page titled \"Salah Mansour.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}